Living Out Loud is a comedy, drama, romance film
directed by Richard LaGravenese.
Judith Moore is suddenly single after discovering her husband of fifteen years, a
successful doctor, has been having an affair with a younger woman.
Judith stews, plans, plots and fantasizes, but she can't decide what to do with her life until she goes
out to a night club to see singer Liz Bailey, who is full of advice on life and love.
While out on the town, Judith is suddenly kissed by a total
stranger, which opens her eyes to new possibilities...
which is when she notices Pat, the elevator operator in her building.
Judith Moore, played by Holly Hunter.
Pat Francato, played by Danny DeVito.
Liz Bailey, played by Queen Latifah.
Robert Nelson, played by Martin Donovan.
Phil Francato, played by Richard Schiff.
The Kisser, played by Elias Koteas.
Living Out Loud is a 1998 American comedy-drama film written and directed by Richard LaGravenese and set in New
York City, starring Holly Hunter, Danny DeVito, Queen Latifah, Martin Donovan, and Elias Koteas.
The film explores themes of infidelity, loss of loved one,
massage, female protagonist, relationship.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.